{
    "subject": "resource/Albert_King",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Blues",
    "human_readable": "Albert King's genre is Blues.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.68327397108078,
            "question": "What musical genre is Albert King associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5483675599098206,
            "question": "Albert King is a prominent figure in which musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48222097754478455,
            "question": "What kind of music characterized Albert King's performances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44395557045936584,
            "question": "What type of music did Albert King play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3840785026550293,
            "question": "What musical style did Albert King help popularize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35901033878326416,
            "question": "Which genre is known for its emotional lyrics and use of the blues scale?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3054254651069641,
            "question": "Albert King's music often conveyed feelings of what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06079960614442825,
            "question": "Which musical genre is known for its improvisational solos and soulful vocals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05478210374712944,
            "question": "Can you name a genre that originated in the African American community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05151025950908661,
            "question": "Give an example of a genre that heavily features the guitar."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Albert King's genre is Blues.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7720_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a genre that originated in the African American community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7720_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which musical genre is known for its improvisational solos and soulful vocals?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7720_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Albert King's music often conveyed feelings of what?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7720_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7720_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided describe Albert King as a blues musician and detail his contributions to the blues genre, supporting the statement that Albert King's genre is Blues."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}